So how was paintball?
Did you have fun?
(Sheldon:)Sure, if you consider being fragged
by your own troops fun.
You clear a space on your calendar.
There will be an inquiry.
(Penny:)Okay. Um...
(Penny:)I'm having a party on Saturday,
so if you're around, come by.
- A party?
- Yeah.
(Howard:)A boy-girl party?
(Penny:)There will be boys
and there will be girls...
(Penny:)...and it is a party, so...
Just a bunch of my friends,
have some beer, do a little dancing.
- Dancing?
- Yeah.
(Leonard:)- I don't know, Penny...
- Thing is, we're not...
- We're really more of a...
- No.
(Leonard:)But thanks.
Thanks for thinking of us.
Are you sure? It's Halloween.
(Sheldon:)A Halloween party?
(Howard:)As in costumes?
(Penny:)Well, yeah.
(Leonard:)Is there a theme?
(Penny:)Um, yeah, Halloween.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but are the costumes random
or genre-specific?
(Penny:)As usual, I'm not following.
(Leonard:)He's asking if we can come as anyone
from science fiction...
(Leonard:)- ...fantasy...
- Sure.
- Comic books?
- Fine.
- Anime?
- Of course.
TV, film, D&D, manga.
Greek, Roman, Norse gods...
(Penny:)Anything you want.
(Penny:)Okay? Any costume you want.
(Penny:)Bye.